<dashboard>
    <label>About</label>
    <row>
        <html>
          <div>
            <h2>Splunk Reference App - Pluggable Auditing System (PAS)</h2>
            <h2>Version 1.5.0 - Build 091515</h2>

            <h3>Getting Started</h3>
            <p class="aboutBox">
              The Pluggable Auditing System (PAS) app and the accompanying guidance will help you  learn how to develop apps for Splunk Enterprise. This end-to-end app was developed by a Splunk engineering team in partnership with <a href="http://www.conducivesi.com">Conducive Consulting</a> and implements real-world use cases. The presented experience includes software development, testing, packaging and publishing a Splunk app. It is not, however, meant, to cover all technological features of the Splunk development platform.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox">
              The app is intended to let an organization monitor various document repositories (current and future). Managers and auditors can use the app to see who has looked at, updated, modified, deleted, or downloaded documents or other artifacts from various sources. By default, the app is configured to use sample data generated on the fly: you may need to wait a few minutes after first installing the app before any data becomes available.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox">
              The app includes a number of dashboards that illustrate some of the capabilities of Splunk Enterprise apps written using SimpleXML and the SplunkJS stack. The app is modular in nature and is designed for extensibility. It includes a number of data provider add-ons to simulate other data sources; these add-ons are hidden by default, but you can view them if you navigate to Manage Apps in your Splunk Enterprise installation. It also ships with a real data provider (Google Drive) and a real custom alert action (Atlassian JIRA) - see the corresponding README for instructions on how to enable and configure them. For the app to function, you need to have at least one data provider add-on installed.
            </p>
          </div>
        </html>
        <html>
          <div>
            <h3>The Dashboards</h3>
            <p class="aboutBox">
              On the dashboards, you will see small lightbulb symbols (<i class="icon-bulb"></i>). If you hover the mouse over any of these you will see some additional information about the panel, and clicking will take you to the relevant location in the guidance.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox"> 
              The <strong>Summary</strong> dashboard provides an overview of activity in the document repositories highlighting policy violations, suspicious activity, and historical trends. Imagine it to be used in a Command &amp; Control Center. The top two panels only show the data since midnight and refresh automatically every 5 mins. 
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox"> 
              The <strong>User Activity</strong> dashboard, that you can navigate to from the list of <strong>Top Users</strong> on the <strong>Summary</strong> dashboard (click on the username, choose Drilldown), lets you focus on the activities of a specific user.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox"> 
              The three <strong>Suspicious Activity</strong> dashboards let you view detailed information about the suspicious activities listed on the Summary dashboard.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox"> 
              The <strong>Customer Monitor</strong> dashboard lets you monitor accesses to documents in the repository associated with specific customers. Example customers in the sample data include Aladdin, Cade, and Ronan.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox"> 
              The <strong>Keycard Activity</strong> dashboard lets you track locations and time of the employees access to company resources and real estate. It aggregates the high volume location data into a choropleth map.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox"> 
              The <strong>Alerts</strong> dashboard lets you set and manage custom alerts triggered by a search.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox">  
              Finally, there is a <strong>Setup</strong> dashboard where you are directed the first time you visit the app. On this dashboard you can specify the list of departments to display on the <b>Summary</b> dashboard and customize how the app calculates the policy violation weighted score. This dashboard uses the KV store to persist the settings.
            </p>
          </div>
        </html>
      </row>
      <row>
        <html>
          <div>
            <h3>Splunk Knowledge Objects</h3>
            <p class="aboutBox">  
              The PAS app makes extensive use of many Splunk knowledge objects that you can view from the <strong>Settings</strong> menu such as:
            </p>
            <ul>
              <li>The PAS Data Model</li>
              <li>Custom event types in each of the provider add-ons</li>
              <li>Custom tags in each of the provider add-ons</li>
              <li>Field aliases, calculated fields, and field extractions in each of the provider add-ons</li>
              <li>Lookups in the <strong>pas_hr_info</strong> app</li>
              <li>Custom alert actions</li>
            </ul>
          </div>
          <div>
            <h3>Additional Resources</h3>
            <p class="aboutBox">  
              In addition to the code base, we are making our test resources available for your reference and learning. These include: test automation suites, unit tests and static test data sets. A simulated identity provider is also made available so that you do not need to procure an LDAP/AD server. These additional resources can be accessed through a separate
              <a href="https://github.com/splunk/splunk-ref-pas-test">repository on GitHub</a>.
            </p>
          </div>
          </html>
          <html>
          <div>
            <h3>Where to Download</h3>
            <ul>
              <li>
                <a href="https://github.com/splunk/splunk-ref-pas-code">Code Repo</a>
              </li>
              <li>
                <a href="https://github.com/splunk/splunk-ref-pas-code">Testing Artefacts Repo</a>
              </li>
              <li>
               <a href="http://dev.splunk.com/goto/devguide">Developer Guide</a>
              </li>
            </ul>
          </div>
          <div>
            <h3>Feedback</h3>
            <p class="aboutBox">  
              Questions, comments, suggestions? To provide feedback about this release, to get help with any problems, or to stay connected with other developers building on Splunk Enterprise please visit <a href="http://answers.splunk.com">answers.splunk.com</a> community site. 
            </p>
            <ul> 
              <li>Email: <a href="mailto:devinfo@splunk.com">devinfo@splunk.com</a></li>
              <li>Blog: <a href="http://blogs.splunk.com/dev">http://blogs.splunk.com/dev</a></li>
              <li>Twitter: <a href="http://twitter.com/splunkdev">@splunkdev</a></li>
            </ul>
            <h3>Support and Community Contributions</h3>
            <p class="aboutBox"> 
              We strongly value user feedback and appreciate your bug reports/feature requests for future releases. Please use <a href="https://github.com/splunk/splunk-ref-pas-code/issues">Issues</a> on GitHub to submit them.
            </p>
            <p class="aboutBox"> 
              You can also contribute to our code base and revise/propose new content for the Splunk Developer Guide. We accept pull requests after you submit your signed <a href="http://dev.splunk.com/view/SP-CAAAEDR">contribution agreement</a>.
            </p>
          </div>
        </html>
      </row>
      <row>
        <html>

          <table width="100%">
            <tr>
              <td width="50%" style="padding-right: 25px;"> 
                <div>
                  <h3>Authors and Contributors</h3>
                  <p class="aboutBox">
                    These are the members of the development team who produced the PAS app and the accompanying guide:
                  </p>
                  <ul>
                    <li>Vision and Product Management: <strong>Grigori Melnik</strong> (Splunk).</li>
                    <li>Business Requirements: <strong>Randy Hammelman</strong> and <strong>Dave Weir</strong> (Conducive Consulting) - your dedication and active involvement in the project was remarkable!</li>
                    <li>Program Management: <strong>Ari Brown</strong> (Splunk)</li>
                    <li>Development: <strong>David Foster</strong>, <strong>Satoshi Kawasaki</strong>, 
                    <strong>Grigori Melnik</strong>, and <strong>David Poncelow</strong> (Splunk), <strong>Brian Schutz</strong>, <strong>Randy Hammelman</strong> and <strong>Praveen Pohar</strong> (Conducive Consulting), <strong>Ashish Bhutiani</strong> (Function1).</li>
                    <li>Ux: <strong>Peter Stern</strong> (Blink Interactive), <strong>Brian Carlos Reyes</strong> (Splunk).</li>
                    <li>Testing: <strong>Liying Jiang</strong> (Splunk).</li>
                    <li>Documentation: <strong>Dominic Betts</strong> (Content Master Ltd.), <strong>Grigori Melnik, Matthew Tevenan, David Foster</strong>, and <strong>Liying Jiang </strong> (Splunk).</li>
                    <li>Documentation Post-Production and Release: <strong>RoAnn Corbisier</strong> (Independent), <strong>Chris Burns</strong> (Independent), <strong>Franck Curier</strong> and <strong>Matthew Tevenan</strong> (Splunk). </li>
                  </ul>
                  <p class="aboutBox">
                            Many thanks to the following people who provided meaningful feedback and support:
                          </p>
                          <ul>
                            <li>Our customers – <strong>Bernie Macias</strong> of Zillow, <strong>Kate Engel</strong> of Morgan Stanley, <strong>Brad Newman</strong> of ViewPost, <strong>Mika Borner</strong> of LC Systems-Engineering – for beta testing the PAS app and reviewing our technical guidance.</li>
                            <li>
                              <strong>Jack Coates</strong> and <strong>Adrian Hall</strong> for insights on extensibility and various aspects of compliance to the Common Information Model.
                            </li>
                            <li><strong>Glenn Block</strong> for diligent review of the questions backlog, validating the HTTP Event Collector scenarios and implementation, continuing advocacy of the project among customers and thoughtful doc reviews.</li>
                            <li><strong>Fred Wilmot</strong> for security review, identifying a vulnerability and helping come up with a better implementation.</li>
                            
                          </ul>
                </div>
              </td>
              <td width="50%" style="padding-left: 5px;">
                <div>
                          <ul>
                            <li><strong>David Carasso</strong> and <strong>Alex Raitz</strong> for validating our approach, asking questions, and providing pointers to the capabilities of Splunk we didn't know existed.</li>
                            <li><strong>Nick Filippi, Matt Elting, Siegfried Puchbauer</strong>, and <strong>Carl Yestrau</strong> for consulting us on the particulars of the UI framework and the Custom Alert Action framework.</li>   
                            <li><strong>Clint Sharp</strong> for many insights on using and trubleshooting eventgen.</li>          
                            <li><strong>Sanford Owings</strong> for the valuable real-world insights on the distributed deployment considerations.</li>
                            <li><strong>Denis Gladkikh</strong> for conducting code reviews and providing ideas for improvements.</li>
                            <li><strong>Mark Groves</strong> for letting us loose, yet providing important suggestions and steering the project.</li>
                            <li><strong>Jon Rooney</strong>, <strong>Misty Gibbs</strong>, and <strong>Erick Mechler</strong> for marketing and communication support.</li>
                             <li><strong>Randy Young, Amrit Bath, Margaret Lee</strong>, and <strong>Alex Munk</strong> for supporting and deploying the PAS app to the Splunk Cloud Sandbox.</li>
                            <li><strong>Chris Bauer</strong>, <strong>Dritan Bitincka</strong>, <strong>Brent Boe</strong>, <strong>Dennis Bourg</strong>, <strong>Jack Coates</strong>, <strong>Damien Dallimore</strong>, <strong>Mark Groves</strong>, <strong>Oleg Izmerly</strong>, <strong>Alex James</strong>, <strong>Satoshi Kawasaki</strong>, <strong>Edward Kostowski</strong>, <strong>Divanny Lamas</strong>, <strong>David Maislin</strong>, <strong>David Noble</strong>, <strong>Sanford Owings</strong>, <strong>David Poncelow</strong>,<strong>Michael Porath</strong>, <strong>Hal Rottenberg</strong>, <strong>Michael Szebenyi</strong>, <strong>Eric Woo</strong>, <strong>Brian Wooden</strong>, <strong>Simeon Yep</strong>, and <strong>Dmitrii Zakharov</strong> for providing feedback on the project and reviewing our technical guidance.</li>                        
                            <li><strong>Damien Dallimore</strong> and <strong>Hal Rottenberg</strong> for evangilising the project.</li>
                            <li><strong>Alex Prokhorenko</strong> and <strong>Terry Martin</strong> for support in publishing and certifying the app.</li>
                            <li><strong>Christopher Gales</strong> for guiding our documentation adventures.</li>
                            <li><strong>Paddy Griffin</strong> and <strong>Rick Roberts</strong> for the metaphors and diagrams that help explain Splunk concepts.</li>
                            <li><strong>Ashwin Kedia</strong> for the initial facilitation of the partnership with Conducive.</li>
                            <li><strong>Ji-Hyun Park</strong> for legal support, <strong>Patricia Iorg, Rendi Miller</strong>, and <strong>Dee Bender</strong> for administrative support .</li>
                            <li><strong>Manish Sainani</strong> for validating our approach to anomaly detection.</li>
                          </ul>
                          <p class="aboutBox">
                          We also thank our executive team for their leadership and ongoing support of our effort: 
                            <strong>Godfrey Sullivan, Stephen Sorkin, Guido Schroeder, Snehal Antani, Doug Merritt, Steve Sommer, Shay Mowlem, Markus Zirn, Krishna Tammana, Carola Thompson</strong>, and <strong>Colin Savage</strong>.
                          </p>
                  </div>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </table>

         
        </html>
      </row>
    
</dashboard>
